{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "League of Legends, DOTA 2, Smite and Heroes of the Storm are all part of which game genre?",
            "correct_answer": "Multiplayer Online Battle Arena (MOBA)",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Real Time Strategy (RTS)",
                "First Person Shooter (FPS)",
                "Role Playing Game (RPG)"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "What is the most expensive weapon in Counter-Strike: Global Offensive?",
            "correct_answer": "Scar-20\/G3SG1",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "M4A1",
                "AWP",
                "R8 Revolver"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Which of these features was added in the 1994 game &quot;Heretic&quot; that the original &quot;DOOM&quot; could not add due to limitations?",
            "correct_answer": "Looking up and down",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Increased room sizes",
                "Unlimited weapons",
                "Highly-detailed textures"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "In what year was the original Sonic the Hedgehog game released?",
            "correct_answer": "1991",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "1989",
                "1993",
                "1995"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "In &quot;Clash Royale&quot; what is Arena 4 called?",
            "correct_answer": "P.E.K.K.A&#039;s Playhouse",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Barbarian Bowl",
                "Spell Valley",
                "Royal Arena"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "What Nationality is D.Va from Overwatch?",
            "correct_answer": "Korean",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Japanese",
                "Chinese",
                "Vietnamese "
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "When was &quot;Garry&#039;s Mod&quot; released?",
            "correct_answer": "December 24, 2004",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "November 13, 2004",
                "December 13, 2004",
                "November 12, 2004"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "What is Gabe Newell&#039;s favorite class in Team Fortress 2?",
            "correct_answer": "Spy",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Heavy",
                "Medic",
                "Pyro"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "In &quot;Overwatch,&quot; an allied McCree will say &quot;Step right up&quot; upon using his ultimate ability Deadeye.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "What type of genre is the controversial 2015 game &quot;Hatred&quot;?",
            "correct_answer": "Shoot &#039;Em Up",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Point &amp; Click",
                "MMORPG",
                "Simulation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In vanilla Minecraft, which of the following cannot be made into a block?",
            "correct_answer": "Charcoal",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Coal",
                "Wheat",
                "String"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "Danganronpa 2: Goodbye Despair featured all of the surviving students from the first game.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "What name does the little headcrab in &quot;Half Life 2&quot; have?",
            "correct_answer": "Lamarr",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Jumperr",
                "Drett",
                "Jerry"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In Sonic the Hedgehog universe, Tails&#039; real name is Miles Prower.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "In the original DOOM games, which of the following demons is a recolor of the Baron of Hell, but is weaker than the Baron?",
            "correct_answer": "Hell Knight",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Mancubus",
                "Pinky",
                "Arch-Vile"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In what year was &quot;Antichamber&quot; released?",
            "correct_answer": "2013",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "2012",
                "2014",
                "2011"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In what year was the game &quot;FTL: Faster Than Light&quot; released?",
            "correct_answer": "2012",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "2014",
                "2013",
                "2011"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "David Baszucki was a co-founder of ROBLOX Corporation.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "What was the first weapon pack for &quot;PAYDAY 2&quot;?",
            "correct_answer": "The Gage Weapon Pack #1",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "The Overkill Pack",
                "The Gage Chivalry Pack",
                "The Gage Historical Pack"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "In &quot;Earthbound&quot;, how does one enter &quot;Master Belch&#039;s&quot; factory?",
            "correct_answer": "Wait 3 Minutes",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Enter the password &quot;Fly Honey&quot;",
                "Enter the password &quot;Master Belch Rules&quot;",
                "Enter the password &quot;Mr Saturn Drools&quot;"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Who is the main protagonist of &quot;Ace Combat Zero: The Belkan War&quot;?",
            "correct_answer": "Cipher",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Mobius 1",
                "Blaze",
                "Pixy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "How many unique items does &quot;Borderlands 2&quot; claim to have?",
            "correct_answer": "87 Bazillion ",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "87 Million",
                "87 Trillion",
                "87 Gazillion "
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "In &quot;Call Of Duty: Zombies&quot;, what is the name of Samantha Maxis&#039; dog?",
            "correct_answer": "Fluffy",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Baxter",
                "Fido",
                "Henry"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "The Khajiit are a race of cat-like creatures from which epic series of role-playing games, set across the land of Tamriel?",
            "correct_answer": "The Elder Scrolls",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Lord of the Rings",
                "The Witcher",
                "Neverwinter Nights"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "What is the name of the main protagonist in &quot;Xenoblade Chronicles&quot;?",
            "correct_answer": "Shulk",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Reyn",
                "Fiora",
                "Dunban"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Which of the following is NOT a Nintendo game console?",
            "correct_answer": "Dreamcast",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "SNES",
                "Wii",
                "Switch"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In &quot;PUBATTLEGROUNDS&quot; which ammo type does the M24 use?",
            "correct_answer": "7.62mm",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "5.56mm",
                "9mm",
                ".300 Magnum"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "&quot;Strangereal&quot; is a fictitious Earth-like world for which game series?",
            "correct_answer": "Ace Combat",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Jet Set Radio",
                "Deus Ex",
                "Crimson Skies"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "In the ARPG &quot;Path of Exile,&quot; what is the highest amount of sockets that an item can have?",
            "correct_answer": "6",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "5",
                "4",
                "8"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "In which U.S. state is Far Cry 5&#039;s fictional setting &#039;Hope County&#039; located?",
            "correct_answer": "Montana",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Idaho",
                "Wyoming",
                "North Carolina"
            ]
        }
    ]
}